[{
        "question": "What is Red's Nationality?",
        "answers": ["Dutch"],
        "footnote": "Red was born in the Netherlands but lived in many other countries during her life"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who programmed SweetyPi?",
        "answers": ["Akashic", "David", "@Akashic"],
        "footnote": "SweetyPi was the first Discord-Bot of Akashic. Since then he programmed many more for others, including DoodleForFood, RedPandaMon and OkBlueComics"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the breed of Sweety?",
        "answers": ["Ragdoll"],
        "footnote": "Red is not the only owner of a Ragdoll in the community. Ektrix also has one"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest role anyone on the server has?",
        "answers": ["The Queen"],
        "footnote": "There are currently over 200 Members in this server, making her role even more rarer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct command to get your level (without the !)",
        "answers": ["level"],
        "footnote": "There are currently 33 commands available on this server"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the nationality of Akashic and Redbeard?",
        "answers": ["German"],
        "footnote": "The mods of this community are from Germany, the Netherlands and America"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many channels are there in the 'Hang out spot'-Category?",
        "answers": ["15", "fifteen"],
        "footnote": "There are 21 channels on this server (or are there more? ;))"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Red's favourite video-game?",
        "answers": ["Portal"],
        "footnote": "The cake is still a lie"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the most seen twitch-highlight of Red?",
        "answers": ["long cat"],
        "footnote": "Long cat became a meme resulting in three emotes and a community challenge on Twitch"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many animated emotes are there on this channel?",
        "answers": ["2", "two"],
        "footnote": "Those two emotes were not planned and were created out of boredom (no regrets there)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Name one result when you type '!shake' on Red's Twitch",
        "answers": ["Stares into your soul",
            "Does nothing",
            "Meows",
            "Headbutts",
            "Demands a treat",
            "Screams",
            "Walks away",
            "Ignores you",
            "Stares",
            "demands headscratches",
            "Shakes paw",
            "Lifts paw"
        ],
        "footnote": "The most used command on Twitch is !hyello"
    }
]